## **Envi Bagus Aditya**

### **UI/UX Designer**

Envi is a highly skilled and motivated UI/UX Designer with a passion for digital products. I bring creative design skills and technical expertise to my projects to make intuitive user-centered designs. Have experience working with teams to analyze and create beautiful product design based on requirements and design thinking process using atomic design approach. I am constantly exploring new technologies and design trends, also have some front-end coding experiences.

### **Experience**



#### NATIVE PRODUCTIONS April 2022 - Present

#### Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part-time • Bali, Indonesia

- Designed low-fidelities and high-fidelities for multiple projects in company correlated with Web2 and Web3.
- > Conducted UX research and interview on several projects from start to end.
- Coded landing pages website projects using HTML, CSS, Javascript for client projects



#### AIRDROP VENTURES PTE. LTD. September 2022 - January 2023

#### UI/UX Designer

Full-time - Semi Remote Singapore

- Designed and Collaborated with teams in total 3 big projects correlated with Web3 from Low-fidelity into High-fidelity
- Organised and Built company complex design system for multiple products in Company.
- UX Researched base requirements and regulation in Indonesia for building products.
- › Directed other UX/UI Designer to maximise workflow in Figma in a tight deadlines utilising Plugins, Shortcuts, Libraries, and Design System.



#### PT. IDOOH BERSAMA INDOESIA June 2022 - October 2022

#### UI/UX Designer

Full-time - Remote • Jakarta, Indonesia

- > Designed and Prototyped multiple products following Tailwind UI style guides.
- Conducted UX Audit some of other products that the company have launch and currently build.
- > Directed 3 UI/UX Designers on teams to maximise the workflow for faster project done.
- > Created complex design system for products and company.
- > Conducted user interview for every new projects, Created user flows, mind map, wireframes, information architecture.



### MERGED, INC. June 2022 - Nov 2022

### Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part-time - Remote • California

- Conducted research about most popular payment banking and payment system in the United States.
- Designed mobile low-fidelity, design system, and high-fidelity of Merged app.
- > Building prototypes, brand guides to be used for pitching and marketing purposes.
- > Created design system for product source of truth



### PT. TIGA TOKEN DIGITAL June 2021 - September 2022

### √∭⊅ UI/UX Designer

Full-time • Bali, Indonesia

- Designed 6+ big projects related to Web3 including NFT Marketplace,
   Crypto Wallet Extension, Crypto Exchange, Staking, and Crypto Launchpad
   as a single UX/UI Designer in company
- › Designed NEFTiPEDiA NFT Marketplace as a main product of company resulted 15,000 Downloaders IOS and Android
- > Coded multiple landing pages for each company website products using HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- > Conducted research about Web3 and Blockchain in designer role.
- > Created graphic design for various events and social media purposes.



### PT. LABELLE PELARIAN INDONESIA Sep - 2019- Nov 2019

# Product Designer

Full-time • Bali, Indonesia

- Designed and Managed versioning of Travel agent website app and Community traveling platform that focusing on women using Figma.
- > Conducted UX Research related to the travel agent product
- > Managed website using Docker and Linux.



### VENTRAPEDIA July 2019- Dec 2020

# Freelance Web Designer

Part-time Pali, Indonesia

- Designed Responsive design of Travel agent website app and Community Platform using Adobe XD.
- Designed dashboard for managing travel platform.
   Coded all the design using HTML, CSS, Javascript with Bootstrap and
- Bulma Frameworks.



# PT. LUMONATA Aug 2017 - Oct 2017

### Web Designer

Internship • Bali, Indonesia

- > Focused learning Web design and Web development with teams.
   > Created some graphic designs using Adobe Photoshop and Adobe
- Illustrator.
- > Participated in multiple website design competitions.
- > Helped some designs and development for the company

#### Contact



Portfolio Website envibagus.netlify.app



Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/envibagus



+62 878 6222 0311

Email envibagus@gmail.com

Location Bali, Indonesia

# Skills

### Design

- › Visual Design
- > Design Thinking
- Mobile Design
- UX ResearchUX Writing
- Web DesignSAAS Design
- > Interaction Design
- > Design System
  - Design Tokens
- > Design Principle
- Figma Libraries
- > Prototyping

### Tools

> Figma

Able to fully maximise features of Figma with plugins, shortcuts, hidden features, and multiple tricks to accelerate workflow for project done.

- › Figjam
- > Zeplin
  > Invision
- > Miro
  > Framer
- > Maze

> Notion

- > Sketch
  > ProtoPie
- > Linear
- > Adobe XD
- Google Workspace
   Microsoft 365
- Adobe IllustratorAdobe Photoshop
- > Atlassian Products

#### **Soft Skills**

- > Problem Solving
- > Project Management
- > Leadership
- > Attention to detail
- CollaborationAdaptability
- > Public Speaking

### Development

HTML & CSS

> Version Control

- > SQL Database
- > Javascript
- › Bootstrap› Tailwind CSS

### Certification & Awards

- Bootcamp UI/UX & Product Management
  Harisenin.com Bootcamp January 2023
- Design Thinking Techniques for Efficiency
  Binar Academy September 2022
- OUX Design for Product Development Skill Academy • March 2020
- 3rd Winner of Web design Paras ICT 2020 Stiki Indonesia • February 2020
- 2nd Winner of National Group Web design Techno Art Universitas Bunda Mulia, Jakarta • April 2019
- 3rd Winner of Web design Paras ICT 2019 Stiki Indonesia • February 2019
- Ist Winner of Web design PNBWDC Politeknik Negeri Bali • September 2018
- 2nd Winner of National Web design Invention Universitas Udayana • June 2018

### Education

> Harisenin.com Bootcamp Product Management and UI/UX August 2022 - January 2023

ITB Stikom Bali
 Bachelor Degree in Information System

 September 2019 - Present

SMK TI Bali Global
 Vocational High school majoring in
 Software Engineering
 July 2016 - July 2019

### Languages

- , Indonesian Native or bilingual proficiency
- English
- Professional working proficiency